[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]
Now we know everything about logistic regression classifiers and
الآن نحن نعرف كل شيء عن مصنفات الانحدار اللوجستي
the representation.
وكيفية تمثيلها.
What the impact of parameters are, how they can be used for classification,
ما تأثير المتغيرات، وكيف يمكن استخدامها عند التصنيف،
how they can be used for multi class classification.
كيف يمكن استخدامها مع المصنفات متعددة الفئات.
That's the foundation we need to talk about linear classifiers and
هذا هو الأساس الذي نحتاج إليه لنتحدث عن المصنفات الخطية
to do the rest of this classification course.
للقيام ببقية دورة التصنيف.
In this module, we're going to dig in and really figure out
في هذه الوحدة، سنتعمق أكثر لنكتشف
how to learn the parameters for the logistic regression classifier.
كيفية تعلم المتغيرات لمصنفات الانحدار اللوجستي.
But let's start with a quick review just to get us in the same mindset.
ولكن دعونا نبدأ بمراجعة سريعة فقط لتجعلنا نفكر بنفس الطريقة.
Now remember, we had this product reviews or restaurant reviews, and
تذكر الآن، كان لدينا مراجعة لمنتج أو مراجعة لمطعم،
we wanted to figure out, for example, that the sushi and everything else were awesome
أردنا أن نعرف، على سبيل المثال، أن السوشي وكل شيء آخر كانوا رائعين
as input has a high probability of being a positive review, while the sushi was good.
فالمدخلات لديها احتمال كبير بأن تكون مراجعة إيجابية. لقد كان السوشي جيدًا.
The service was okay has a probability of only 0.55 of being a positive review.
والخدمة لا بأس بها باحتمال من 0.55 فقط من كونها مراجعة إيجابية.
In other words, we want to learn a classifier of the form probability of y
وبعبارة أخرى، نحن نريد أن نتعلم المصنفات من احتمالية y
given x, where y is the output label positive and negative review and
بالنظر إلى x، حيث y تمثل المخرج والمراجعة الإيجابية والسلبية
x is the input sentence, the actual review.
و x هي جملة الإدخال، أو المراجعة الفعلية.
So we talked about this task and we discussed linear classifiers where with
وتحدثنا عن هذه المهمة و ناقشنا المصنفات الخطية
an associate a weight where a coefficient with every input feature,
حيث ربطنا كل النقاط بوزن أو معامل مع كل ميزة إدخال،
in our case, would be worse like good, great, awesome and so
في حالتنا، هي كلمات مثل جيد، رائع، مذهل وهكذا.
on and positive words may have positive coefficients and
والكلمات الإيجابية قد يكون لها معاملات إيجابية وقد تحتوي الكلمات السلبية على معاملات سلبية.
negative words may have negative coefficients.
وهو النموذج، حيث نحدد الدوال الرئيسية،
Of the coefficients [INAUDIBLE] words appear in that particular
للمعاملات لأي من الكلمات التي تظهر
input centers and that's [INAUDIBLE] from minus infinity to plus infinity.
في جمل الإدخال المعينة، وقد تختلف تلك الدرجة من اللانهاية السالبة إلى اللانهاية الموجبة.
So, we squeeze that into the line 01 to be able to
لذا، نضغط ذلك في الخط من 0 إلى 1 حتى نتمكن من
predict the probability that the review is positive given
توقع احتمالية أن تكون المراجعة إيجابية
the text of the review and the logistic regression model, that probability is
بالنظر إلى نص المراجعة، وفي نموذج الانحدار اللوجستي، هذا الاحتمال
defined by 1 over 1 plus e to the minus w transposed h.
محدد من خلال 1 مقسومًا على 1 زائد e بالقوة الأسية w بالتبادل مع h.
So we explored this quite a bit in the last module.
قمنا باستكشاف هذا قليلًا في الوحدة السابقة.
Just want to warm us up and
ولكن لا بأس من تنشيط المخ
get us into how do we learn these particular coefficients w hat from data.
والتعمق في كيفية تعلم معاملات w hat المعينة من البيانات.
[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]